question_data1 = [
    {"question": "A slug's blood is green.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it "
                 "home to eat.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
     "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "correct_answer": "True"}
]

question_data2 = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Norwegian producer Kygo released a remix of the song &quot;Sexual Healing&quot; by Marvin Gaye.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "E = MC3",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The "
                 "Reckoning&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A &#039;Millinillion&#039; is a real number.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Fiat Multipla is a drivable car in &quot;Forza Horizon 3&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was "
                 "Diamond.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS "
                 "port of the game. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
]
